https://www.cemeterydance.com/privacy-policy.html

F. Paul Wilson
Every Book (All Authors)
Cemetery Dance Auctions
More...
Auctions
(Free Reads!)
Home/ Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We’re glad you chose to visit our website! We care about your privacy and the information you share with us and want you to understand how we are using and protecting the information we collect about you. CemeteryDance.com is respectful of data privacy and adopts best practice in compliance with applicable privacy law and regulations, including the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).
This privacy policy describes the information (personal data) we collect from you, and how it may be stored and processed in the United States of America, as described below.
If you are a European Union (EU) resident, please note that there are a number of provisions in this privacy policy that apply uniquely to you.
What personal data do we collect from the people that visit our website?
We may collect the following personal data:
Contact information, such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number;
Billing information, such as credit or debit card number and billing address;
Unique identifiers, such as user name, account number, and password;
Preferences information you provide, such as product or content interests, or communication or marketing preferences;
Usage activity about how you interact with us, such as purchase history, what content you viewed, and which areas of our Websites you visited; and
Information about your business, such as company name, company size, and business type.
Tracking Technologies
We, or third parties contracted by us, may use technologies such as scripts, to gather information about how you and others interact with our website, and which products and services may be of interest to you. For example, we will know how many users access specific areas or features within our website, and which links or ads they clicked on.
We use Hotjar in order to better understand our users’ needs and to optimize this service and experience. Hotjar is a technology service that helps us better understand our users experience (e.g. how much time they spend on which pages, which links they choose to click, what users do and don’t like, etc.) and this enables us to build and maintain our service with user feedback. Hotjar uses cookies and other technologies to collect data on our users’ behavior and their devices (in particular device's IP address (captured and stored only in anonymized form), device screen size, device type (unique device identifiers), browser information, geographic location (country only), preferred language used to display our website). Hotjar stores this information in a pseudonymized user profile. Neither Hotjar, nor we, will ever use this information to identify individual users or to match it with further data on an individual user. For further details, please see Hotjar’s privacy policy.
You can opt-out to the creation of a user profile, Hotjar’s storing of data about your usage of our site and Hotjar’s use of tracking cookies on other websites by following this opt-out link.
Opting Out of Tracking
If you wish to opt-out, please enable Do Not Track mode in your browser.
Cookies
This site also collects and stores certain information automatically using cookies and similar technologies, including IP addresses, the region or general location of a computer or device accessing the internet, devise type, browser type, operating system, page view history, and other usage information. See our
Cookie Policy for further details.
However, to the extent that any cookie can uniquely identify a computer, mobile device, or tablet (“Device”), or the person using that Device, and you are a EU resident, under the GDPR, this is personal data.  Therefore, this privacy policy shall apply to such personal data collected by CemeteryDance.com.
How do we use your personal data?
We may use this information to:
Fulfill your order
Send you an order confirmation
Send notices of updates to our policies, terms and conditions, and other administrative communications.
Assess your needs to determine suitable products or services
Send you requested product or service information
Send product updates, replacement, or warranty information
Respond to customer service requests
Follow up with user after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)
Administer your account
Send you a newsletter
Send you marketing communications
Administer a contest, promotion, survey, or other site feature
Ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
Improve CemeteryDance.com's Websites and marketing efforts
Conduct research and analysis
Respond to your questions and concerns
Display content based upon your interests
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you visit our site, create an account, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, or enter information on our site.
What happens if you don’t provide personal data?
In order for us to provide the products, content or services you request, we need your personal data. Therefore, if you do not provide such personal data, we cannot deliver the products, content or services.
Security of Your Personal Data
The security of your personal information is important to us.
CemeteryDance.com maintains safeguards, which include technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorized use, access, inadvertent disclosure, alteration, and destruction, and we require the third parties we contract with to support CemeteryDance.com's business operations to employ reasonable security measures as well.
In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
All credit card transactions are processed through a third party gateway provider, and are not stored, or processed, on our servers.
Keep in mind, that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure and so we cannot guarantee its absolute security. In lieu of that, please do not email unencrypted credit card information to us. We also ask that you not send or disclose to us, through our services or otherwise, any other sensitive personal information, such as social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, biometric data (for the purpose of uniquely identifying a natural person), data concerning health or a natural person's sex life or sexual orientation, or criminal background.
The Legal Basis We Have For Processing Your Personal Data
The GDPR requires data collectors, such as CemeteryDance.com, to have a legal basis to use the personal data of EU residents. Therefore, this section shall apply to any such personal data collected by CemeteryDance.com.
CemeteryDance.com uses the personal data that you provide to supply you with high-quality products, content and services as you request, to send important notices, and for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to provide you with the information you need to make the most informed purchase decisions.
We may also use your personal data to offer you products, content or services that may be of interest to you, based upon your interests or the preferences you shared with us.
The legal basis for processing your personal data is your consent. In certain circumstances we may otherwise process your personal data if CemeteryDance.com has a legitimate interest in doing so and CemeteryDance.com is not infringing any of your rights and freedoms.
When CemeteryDance.com processes your personal data for CemeteryDance.com’s legitimate interests, CemeteryDance.com will consider and balance any potential impact on you and your rights under data protection and any other relevant law. Our legitimate business interests do not override your interests. CemeteryDance.com will not use your personal data in circumstances where your rights and freedoms override our legitimate interests, unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law.
When and How We Share Your Personal Data With Others
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal data to outside parties.
As Required By Law
Your personal data may be shared when authorized by law or necessary to comply with a valid legal process.
How Long We Keep Your Personal Data
We retain your personal data for the duration of your business relationship with us, and as long as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, or as needed to provide you services.
If you wish to cancel your account, or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us atCemeteryDance.com
Confirming Your Personal Data
This section shall apply to any personal data collected by CemeteryDance.com from EU residents.
To confirm that CemeteryDance.com is processing your personal data, or to access, update or correct the personal data CemeteryDance.com holds about you, or to obtain a copy to reuse for your own purposes, please send an email to:CemeteryDance.com
Erasing Your Personal Data
This section shall apply to any personal data collected by CemeteryDance.com from EU residents.
If you want your personal data erased, please send an email to:CemeteryDance.com
To Opt-Out of Marketing Communications
If you want CemeteryDance.com to stop communicating with you for marketing purposes, please send an email to:CemeteryDance.com
To Restrict Processing of Your Personal Data
If you want to otherwise restrict CemeteryDance.com’s processing of your personal data, please send an email to:CemeteryDance.com
PayPal
If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal's privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal website.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
CAN-SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
Send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.
To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM, we agree to the following:
NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If, at any time, you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and you will be removed from our mailing list.
Contacting Us
If there are questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact our Data Protection Officer using the information below.
Brian Freeman
c/o Cemetery Dance Publications
132-B Industry Lane, Unit #7, Forest Hill, MD 21050
privacy@cemeterydance.com
Last Edited on 08-06-2018
Shop By Category
Authors Cemetery Dance Books Grave Tales Comic Book Dark Screams series Cemetery Dance eBooks Halloween Carnival series Featured Preorders Cemetery Dance Magazine Other Items (ALL) Stephen King's Doubleday Years Six Book Set! Cemetery Dance Publications "Not-For-Sale" Books! "Preorder Only" Special Editions
Copyright © 1988 - 2020 Cemetery Dance Publications / Performance Website by 2C
